hellokids.com 2016-10-22

# Footer - Privacy Policy

**COBALINK PRIVACY POLICY for Hellokids.com  
**

The Internet is an amazing tool. It has the power to change the way we live, and we're starting to see that potential today. With only a few mouse-clicks, you can follow the news, look up facts and communicate with others from around the world. It's important to COBALINK to help our customers retain their privacy when they take advantage of all the Internet has to offer. 

We believe your business is no one else's. Your privacy is important to you and to us. So we'll protect the information you share with us. To protect your privacy, COBALINK follows different principles in accordance with world-wide practices for customer privacy and data protection.

 We won't sell or give away your name, mail address, email address or any other information to anyone.   
We'll use state-of-the-art security measures to protect your information from unauthorized users.

 **NOTICE**

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally this information is requested when you create a Registration ID on the site or enter a contest. We use your Personal Information for four primary purposes:

 \- To make the site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once.  
\- To help us create content most relevant to you.  
\- To alert you to special offers, updated information and other new services from COBALINK.

 **  
CONSENT**

If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use most of HELLOKIDS.COM. But you will not be able to access areas that require registration. 

If you decide to register, you will be able to select the kinds of information you want to receive from us by subscribing to various services. If you do not want us to communicate with you about other offers regarding COBALINK programs, events, or services by e-mail, you may select the option stating that you do not wish to receive marketing messages from COBALINK. 

COBALINK occasionally allows other companies to offer our registered customers information about their products and services, using email only. If you do not want to receive these offers, you may select the option stating that you do not wish to receive marketing materials from third parties.

 **ADVERTISING**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

The link for “click here” is [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

 **ACCESS**

We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time at Your personal account. There, you can:

 \- View and edit personal information you have already given us.  
\- Sign up for electronic newsletters.  
\- Register. Once you register, you won't need to do it again. Wherever you go on HELLOKIDS, your information stays with you.

 **SECURITY**

COBALINK has taken strong measures to protect the security of your personal information and to ensure that your choices for its intended use are honored. We take strong precautions to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. 

COBALINK strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. 

Your personal information is never shared outside the company without your permission, except under conditions explained above. Inside the company, data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access. 

You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can see or edit your personal information without knowing your user name and password, so do not share these with others.

 **NOTICE TO PARENTS**

Parents or guardians: we want to help you guard your children's privacy. We encourage you to talk to your children about safe and responsible use of their Personal Information while using the Internet. 

If for some reason you believe COBALINK has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by e-mail at support@hellokids.com, and we will do our best to determine and correct the problem promptly. Be certain the words Privacy Policy are in the Subject line.

 **SAFETY OF THE MINORS**

By safety for the minors, any mention of coordinates of the authors is not published or diffused. 

There is no link towards unchecked websites towards the outside of "Hellokids" so that the juniors cannot meet themselves on a not advisable website. These external links are in limited number and we visit them Regularly; nevertheless, we cannot exclude the risk that a series of successive hypermedia links succeeds on content not intended for the minors. We deeply recommend to the parents to watch the safety of their children on Internet. 

All the texts are read before publication.   
Any sending not convenient is not published (rudeness, racism, violence).  
The publication is the object of a selection, are more rarely accepted some adults' works for the children (tales and drawings).   
Even if we try hard to publish all the children's productions, Hello kids, reserves the right to refuse a publication, for material or moral motives without justification. 

**WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION YOU SHARE**

When your child joins us, he/she provides us with personal information, including name and email address. 

COBALINK will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on COBALINK or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of COBALINK and its family of Web sites, and, (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of COBALINK, its Web sites, or the public.

Website WWW.HELLOKIDS.COM is property of the company COBALINK S.A.S., 227 rue Jean Jaurès, 83000 Toulon. This last one is declared with the CNIL under N 697375.

The US website is published by  **COBALINK US  Incorporation -**  **Court House Tower - 44 West Flagler Street - Suite 2300, Miami, FL 33130**
